

PERSONAL PROFILE

Extremely motivated to constantly develop my skills and grow professionally. I am confident in my ability to come up with interesting ideas for unforgettable work. Dedicated and energetic photographer with experience in food & baverage photography. Competent at capturing high quality images and organizing materials for photoshoots while displaying confidence and professionalism at all times.

EDUCATION

Universitas Negeri Malang Bachelor in Educational Technology, 2015

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead Photographer

- Book Menu for Brothers Chicken & Shake Malang
- Book Menu for Ramen Moshi Malang
- Book Menu for Papertown Malang
- Book Menu for Coto Makasar Widodaren Malang
- Book Menu for Sayap Grak Malang
- Book Menu for Fish O Chick Malang
- Photo Stock for Taichan Nyot2 Malang
- Photo Stock for Catering Loemintoe Malang
- Photo Stock for 7 Seven Chicken Malang
- Colaboration project with Magnum Ice Cream x Foodinhands
- Colaboration project with Nutrifood (Nutrisari Kelapa Muda, W'dank Bajigur, & Tropicana Slim Stevia)
- Colaboration project with Exlusive Guide Book (EBC) for Malang, Batu Culinary & Nongkrong Recommended

Assistant Photographer

- Book Menu for Dialogue Food & Coffee Kediri
- Book Menu for Bius Cafe & Resto Malang
- Book Menu for Mommy Manggo Salad Malang
- Book Menu for Brown Tiger Malang



CONTACT

- BANYUWANGI
- 0888-0534-7622
- @hobimakan.banyuwangi@andrea.tya

WORK EXPERIENCE

Photographer for

- MalangFoodies (2018-2019)
- Mlggoodfood (2019)
- Mlggoodplace (2019)
- Ammamamo (2018-2019)
- Foody Floody (2018-2020)
- Hobimakan.Banyuwangi (2020-Now)

Key Opinion Leader for

- Speaker For KANTJATAROENA Photography Roemah Kantja (2019)
- Speaker for Sharing Sesion Food Photography for Simpati TAP Branch Malang (2019)
- KOL for Diatab NAKAM-NAKAM Malang (2019)
- Speaker for Online Seller Workshop Grab Express Surabaya (2019)
- Speaker for Online Workshop SMA Muhammadiyah 6 Malang (2020)
- Speaker for Creativepreneur Talks di SMK PGRI 2 Giri Banyuwangi (2021)
- Speaker for FOODPRENUER BANYUWANGI series 1 Osing Deles (2021
- Speaker for TALENT TALK Banyuwangi Talent Hub KEMENAKER RI (2021)